const decks = {
  'Geography': {
    title: 'Geography',
    cards: [
      {
        question: 'What are the living components of an ecosystem?',
        answer: 'Flora, fauna and bacteria are the living components of an ecosystem.'
      },
      {
        question: 'What are the non-living components of an ecosystem?',
        answer: 'Climate, soil and water are the non-living components of an ecosystem.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is a producer?',
        answer: 'The producer provides the basic source of food, eg a plant',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is a food web?',
        answer: 'A food web includes all of the connections between producers and consumers in an ecosystem.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What factor determines the distribution of large-scale ecosystems?',
        answer: 'Climate determines the distribution of large-scale ecosystems. ',
      },
      {
        question: 'What weather conditions are associated with low-pressure areas?',
        answer: 'Cloud and precipitation are associated with low-pressure areas.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What weather conditions are associated with high-pressure areas?',
        answer: 'Dry and warm weather conditions are associated with high -pressure areas.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What large-scale ecosystem would you expect to find at the Equator?',
        answer: 'Tropical rainforests are found at the Equator.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What large-scale ecosystem would you expect to find 30째N and 30째S of the Equator?',
        answer: 'Deserts are found 30째N and 30째S of the Equator. ',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is a biome?',
        answer: 'A biome is a large-scale ecosystem.',
      },
    ],
  },
  'Electromagnetic Spectrum': {
    title: 'The Electromagnetic Spectrum',
    cards: [
      {
        question: 'Which of these types of electromagnetic radiation has the lowest energy? Microwaves, Radio waves, Infrared.',
        answer: 'Radio waves have lower energy than either microwaves or infrared.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these types of electromagnetic radiation has the highest frequency? Gamma, X-rays, Ultraviolet.',
        answer: 'Gamma waves have the highest frequency of all electromagnetic radiation.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of these types of electromagnetic radiation has the shortest wavelength? Infrared, Visible light, Ultraviolet.',
        answer: 'Ultraviolet has a shorter wavelength than either infrared or visible light.'
      },
      {
        question: 'What can split white light into its component colours? A prism, A disperser, A protractor.',
        answer: 'A prism splits white light into its component colours.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Which colour of light is refracted the furthest? Red, Green, Violet.\n',
        answer: 'Violet light is refracted the furthest.',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which type of electromagnetic radiation travels faster? Radio waves, Gamma, They both travel at the same speed.',
        answer: 'All types of electromagnetic radiation travel at the same speed.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is infrared used for? Night vision, Communication, Cooking',
        answer: 'Infrared is used for night vision.',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which type of electromagnetic radiation is used to sterilise food? Beta, Gamma, Alpha.',
        answer: 'Gamma waves are used to sterilise food and medical equipment.',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which type of UV has the highest hazard level? UVB, UVC, UVA.',
        answer: 'UV C has the highest hazard level of all UV types.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of electromagnetic radiation is used by mobile phones? Microwave, Radio wave, X-rays.',
        answer: 'Microwaves are used by mobile phones.',
      },
    ]
  },
}

export default decks